Welcome to the annual charmville crystal carnival.
欢迎来到今年的魔幻城水晶嘉年华
Little charmers,look at the parade.
伙伴们 快看巡游
-So cool. -It's spark-tastic.
-好棒哦 -太棒了
The crystal carnival is such a charm-tastic day.
水晶嘉年华简直就是盛世狂欢
You know it! I wish it was every day.
说得对 真希望每天都是这样
And every night and lots of hours in between.
还有每晚 还有每分每秒
- There are so many things to do at the carnival. - I want to play mini-wand ball.
-这里有好多好玩的啊 -我想去玩迷你魔杖球
And I want to try rainbow roller. I love all the colors!
我想试试那个彩虹滑梯 每个颜色都好漂亮
And this is the year that I finally beat the crystal pixie popper ball game.
今年我一定会赢得水晶杯 精灵球大赛的最终冠军
And get the limited edition Extremely awesome vintage crystal ball.
拿到限量版的超炫复古水晶球